Our second assignment involves various
我们第二个大作业涵盖了许多
modifications to be done to the index.html file that
对你上个练习中得到的 index.html
you had at the end of the last exercise of this module.
的更改
To this page, you're going to add some fonts,
在这个页面中 你需要加入一些字体
some buttons, and a media object, and also a label.
一些按钮 一个多媒体对象和一个标签
The current state of the index.html page is as shown here.
index.html 当前的状态是是这样的
There are four tasks to be completed in this assignment.
然后你需要完成 4 项任务
The first task is to include a form
第一个任务 在导航栏中实现一个表
within your nav bar that allow the users to input their
在这个表里面 用户将会输入
registration information for this website and login into the website.
它们的注册信息以登录进我们的网站
Of course, you just include the form at this moment,
当然你只需要将这个表的前端实现
it will not work at this moment.
而不用去实现后端的登录功能
The contents of this form should be like this.
表的内容应当如图所示
So, explore the nav bar forms in more
你可能需要更好地理解 Bootstrap 之后
detail on the Bootstrap side to understand how you would design something like this.
才能实现一个像这样的表
The second task of your assignment
第二项任务
is to include a button here.
是在这里实现一个按钮
This button should be included in its own div here,
这个按钮应该放在一个单独的 div 里面
so notice that this is occupying the left over space
注意到它应该占据完
in this row of this.
这一行剩下的空间
Now this button, when you click on it, it will take you down to a form at
同时在你点击这个按钮时 它会导航至一个表格
the bottom, which the users can use to preserve their table on this restaurant.
这个表格使用来向餐厅预约的
When you click on the button It will take you down to a form,
当你点击这个按钮 它会将页面导航至页面底部
which is at the bottom of this page.
的一个表格处
Now this form is included as another row in the content of the webpage here.
然后这个表格将会是你网页的另一个 row-content
Now what does this form contain?
这个表格将会包含什么信息呢？
This form contains information that the users need to submit
它将会包含用户需要向餐厅提交的
in order to reserve on the website.
用来预约的所有信息
So here we have a set of radio buttons that allow us to
我们需要做的 首先是一串单选按钮
select the number of guests, and then we have a Date and Time specification here.
它们将提供预约人数的信息 然后是两个 分别提供预约日期和时间的输入框
Now, notice in particular inside the Date and Time
注意到在这两个输入框中
boxes here, you have the glyphicons for the date and time included.
我们会有两个 glyphicons 小图标来让它更好看
Again, read the forms in the Bootstrap
关于怎么实现
documentation to understand how you would put glyphicons inside there.
需要看 Bootstrap 的文档
And of course you have the action button here.
当然 你还需要一个按钮
Which, when clicked should, of course obviously at this stage,
来提交这些信息
this form will not work, but you should have all these in place.
当然 你不用实现这个表格的后端 不过在这个大作业的最后
In the, at the end of this assignment.
你需要把这些前端的东西都实现了
Now, another part that you will have here is an alert being displayed here.
你还需要在这里显示一个警告
This alert in particular has a link also embedded in here.
这个警告还含有一个链接
And also a cross button embedded in here.
和一个小叉叉来关掉它
Again, study alerts to understand how you will design this warning alert.
如果你不知道怎么实现 就看一看之前的视频 或者参考一下文档吧
This is part of this column that includes the font.
这里还需要你用上字体
Our final task is to apply the media object class
我们最后的任务是在网页的第二行
to the second row of this page.
实现一个多媒体对象
Recall that we applied the media object class to the first and the third row,
我们已经在第一和第三行实现了多媒体对象
but we left the second row untied, and
但我们当时没做第二行
I mentioned that we will do that as part of the second assignment.
我说过这将是第二次大作业的任务 希望你们还记得
In here I am using a media object.
这里我用了多媒体对象
In particular note that the image is displayed to the right
需要特别注意的我将图片放在了右边
after content rather than to the left as we did for the other.
而不是那些文本内容的左边
Also this should include a label here
我们还需要实现一个标签
with the word New inside the label.
标签中的文本应该是 New
This completes your second assignment.
以上 我们说完了第二次大作业的要求
So at the end of this assignment, your webpage should look like this.
那么当你完成了这次大作业后 你的网页应该长这样
First, it should have a way for the user to enter the login information.
首先 需要有一个表来让用户完成登录
Second, there should be a button here that when clicked,
第二 这里应该有一个按钮 而且当你点击它时
will take the user to a reservation form.
它会将用户导航到一个预约表格
Third, there will be a reservation form at the bottom,
第三 这个预约表格应该在网页的最底部
which includes the selection of the number of guests and date and time.
它将会有一串单选按钮和两个输入 日期 时间的输入框
And also an alert being displayed there.
同时这里还需要有一个警告
Dismissable alert being displayed there.
一个可以关掉的警告
And then finally, of course,
而第二步骤在完成5分钟的工作后就停止了
the second row being styled properly using a media object.
你需要将第二行的对媒体对象设置好
The image here Is already provided for
这里用的图片已经在你早些时候下载的
you in the IMG folder that you downloaded earlier.
img 文件夹里面提供了
This image is called the buffet.png.
这张图的名字叫 buffet.png
And the label to be displayed here.
最后就是 这里需要有一个标签 【翻译 - Carefree0910】